in the last video we work through an
example of using a computation graph to
compute a function J now let's take a
cleaned up version at their computation
graph and show how you can use it to
figure out derivative calculations for
that function J so here's a computation
graph let's say you want to compute the
derivative of J with respect to B so
what is that well this says if we were
to take this value of B and change it a
little bit how would the value of J
change well J is defined as um V times D
and right now B is equal to 11 so then
with the bump up B by a little bit to 11
point oo 1 then J which is currently 33
will end up being bumps up to V times a
new value of V becomes 33 0.001 and so
if you bump up V by 0.001 um then J
which is 3 D so currently 33 will get
bumped up to 33 point zero 3 so here
we've increased V by 0.001 and the net
result of that is that J goes up three
times as much so the derivative of J of
respect to B is equal to three because
the increase in J is three times the
increase in V and in fact this is very
analogous to the example we had in the
previous video where we had on F of a
equals three a and so we then derive
that DF da which was slightly simplified
letting sloppy notation you can read it
d FD a was equal to three
right so instead here we have um J
equals BB and so DJ D V is equal to
three with here J playing the role of F
and V playing the role of a in this
previous example that we had right from
from an earlier video so indeed
terminology of backpropagation what
we're seeing is that if you want to
compute the derivative of this final
output variable which usually is a
variable you care most about with
respect to B then we've done you know
sort of one step of back propagation so
we've gone one step backwards in this
graph now let's look at another example
what is DJ da in other words if we bump
up the value of a how does that affect
the value of J well let's go through the
example right now a is equal to five so
let's bump it up to five point zero one
the net impact of that is at D which was
a plus u so that was previous 11 this we
can increase the eleven point zero one
and then we've already seen as above
that J now gets bump up to thirty three
point zero zero three so what we've seen
is that if you increase a by 0.001 J
increases by point zero three and by
increase a I mean maybe you were to take
this value five and just plug in a new
value right then the change to a will
propagate to the rights of the
computation graph so the J ends up being
thirty three point zero three and so the
increase the J is three times the
increase to a so that means this
derivative is equal to three and one way
to break this down is to say that if you
have if you change a then that will
change V and through changing B that
will change a and so the net change to
the value of J when you bump up the
value and when you nudge the value of a
up a little bit is that um first by
changing a you end up increasing B well
how much does D increase right it is
increased by an amount determined by DV da
and then the change in V will cause the
value of J to also increase so in
calculus is actually called the chain
rule that is a affects V of X J then the
amount that J changes where you nudge a
is the product of how much V changes
when you nudge a times how much J
changes when you nudge B so in calculus
um the gate is called the chain rule and
what we saw from this calculation is
that if you increase a by point zero one
V changes by the same amount so DV da is
equal to one so in fact if you plug in
what we have worked our previously Oh
DVD J is equal to three and DVD a is
equal to one so the product of these
three times one then I should give you
the correct value that DJ da is equal to
3 so this illustration shows how by
having computed DJ DV of this derivative
respect to this variable it can then
help you to compute DJ da and so that's
another step within some backward
calculation I'll just introduce one more
new notational convention which is that
in when you're writing code to implement
back-propagation they'll usually be some
final output variable that you really
care about right so the final output
variable that you really care about
whether you want to optimize and in this
case this final output variable is Jane
is really the last node in your
computation graph and so a lot of the
computations will be trying to compute
the derivative of that you know final
output variable so D of this final
output variable with respect to some
other variable and just call that D fall right
so a lot of the computations you have
would be to compute the derivative of
the final output variable really J in
this case with various intermediate
variables such as ABC U or V and when
you implement this in software you know
what you call this variable name alright
one thing you could do is in in Tison
you can write you know give us a very
long variable name ID final output of
all over a diva but that's a very long
variable name you could call this a get
DJ d bar but because you're always
taking derivatives respect to DJ respect
to this final output variable I'm going
to introduce a new notation we're in
code when you are computing this thing
um in the code you write we're just
going to use the variable name d VAR in
order to represent that quantity okay so
d VAR in the code you write will
represent the derivative of the final
output variables you care about such as
J or sometimes the loss L with respect
to the various intermediate quantities
in computing in your code so this thing
here in your codes you know you use them
DV to denote this value so DV would be
equal to 3 and your cold you
representatives as on da right which is
a we also figured out to be equal to 3
okay so um with Sun back propagation
partially through this computation graph
let's go through the rest of this
example on the next slide so let's go to
a cleaned up copy of the computation
graph and just to recap what we've done
so far is go backward here and figured
out that DV is equal to 3 the gain the
definition of DV that's just the
variable name of the code is really DJ
DV I will figured out that D a is equal
to 3 and again da is the variable name
in your code and that's really the value
of DJ
da and what sort of hand wave how you
know we've gone backwards on these two
edges like so now let's keep computing
derivatives or let's look at the value
you so what is DJ vu well through a
similar calculation is what we did
before and we start off with u equals 6
if you bump up you to the 6.01
then V which is previous 11 goes up to
11 point over 1 and so J goes from 33 -
33 point 0 3 and so the increase in J is
3 X so this is equal and the analysis
that U is very similar to the analysis
we did for a this is actually computed
as a DJ DV x DV d you wear this we had
already figured out was 3 and this turns
out to be equal to 1 so we've kind of
one more step back application we end up
computing that D U is also equal to 3
and D U is of course just as DJ gu now
we just step through one last example in
detail so what is DJ DP right so you
imagine if you are allowed to change the
value of B and you want to tweak be a
little bit in order to minimize or
maximize the value of J alright so what
is the derivative what's the slope of
this function J when you change the
value of B a little bit it turns out
that using the chain rule for calculus
this can be written as the product of
two things is DG j vu times d u DB and
the reasoning is if you change be a
little bit so b goes from 3 to say the
point 0 1 um the way of no effect Jane
is it will first affect you so how much
does it affect you well U is defined as
B times C right so this will go from six
when B is equal to 3/2 now our 6.00 to
right because C is equal to 2 in our
example here and so this tells us that
PUD B is equal to 2 because when you
pump up B by point O 1 you increase this
twice as much so d UD b this is equal to
2 and now we know that U has gone up
twice as much as B has gone up
well once DJ D you we've already figured
out that this is equal to 3 and so by
multiplying these two out we find that
DJ DB is equal to 6 and again
here's the reasoning for the second part
of the argument which is we want to know
when you goes up by point over to how
does that affect J the fact that DJ D U
is equal to 3 that tells us that when
you goes up by point zero two J goes up
three times as much so J should go up by
0.06 right so so bill that's comes from
in fact that DJ d u is equal to three
and if you check the map in detail you
will find that if B becomes three point
zero one then you become six point zero
two V becomes 11.0 - all right so that's
a plus u so this 5 Plus u and then J
which is equal to 3 times V then ends up
being equal to 33 point zero zero six
right and so that's how you get that DK
DB is equal to 6 and to fill that in
this is if we go backwards so this is DB
is equal to 6 and DD really is the
Python code variable name for you know
DJ dB
and I won't I won't go through the last
example in great detail but it turns out
that if you also computes out DJ da this
turns out to be DJ b u times d u da and
this turns out to be ninth it turns out
these three times three I won't go
through that example in detail Pacelle
through this last step you know it is
possible to derive that B C is equal to
so the key takeaway from this video from
this example is that when computing
derivatives in computing all of these
derivatives the most efficient way to do
so is through a right-to-left
computation following the direction of
the event arrows and in particular we'll
first compute the derivative respect to
B and then that becomes useful for
computing the derivative respect to a
and the derivative with respect to U and
then the derivative respect to u for
example this term for example this term
over here and this term over here those
in turn become useful for computing to
their servers going to be in the
director of respect to C so that was a
computation drop and how there's a
forward or left to right calculation to
compute the cost function such as JD you
might want to optimize and a backward or
a right to left calculation to compute
derivatives if you're not familiar with
calculus or the chain rule I know some
of those details would have gone by
really quickly but you didn't follow all
the details don't worry about it in the
next video we'll go for this again in
the context of logistic regression and
show you exactly what you need to do in
order to implement the computations you
need to compute the derivatives of the
logistic regression model